## Parul Sharma

### Marketing Automation Specialist

- India
- ✓ sparul247@gmail.com
- +919015009656
- R Portfolio Website
- in LinkedIn
- GitHub



#### PROFILE

I have an overall experience of more than 3.5 years in different business verticals. I have experience in marketing automation, data analytics, product development and services, planning and team management. Further to enhance my skills in today's data-driven AI world, I have good knowledge of Statistics, Data Visualization, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and Natural Language Processing.

#### **EDUCATION**

2010 - 2014

Baddi, India

2008 - 2010

Solan, India

Bachelors of Technology in Electronics and Communication,

Baddi University 🛮

**High School,** MRA DAV ☑



#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 – present Panchkula, India Marketing Automation Specialist, Grazitti Interactive ☑ Roles and Responsibilities

- Working dedicatedly on Demand generation programs like Webinars, Product Tours and Sales Demo development.
- Email Engagement programs
- Social engagement programs with Gatted assets for Linkedin, Google, Instagram and other ad websites.
- Working on operational campaigns like Lead Scoring and Data Normalization
- Marketo Instance Audit

#### Tools used

• Adobe Marketo Engage, ON24, Webex, Litmus, MS-Excel

Oct 2020 – Dec 2020

Panchkula, India

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020

Bengaluru, India

Marketing Automation Intern, Grazitti Interactive ☑

• Worked on the Adobe Marketo Engage, Adobe's marketing automation tool

**Data Science Intern**, *iNeuron* □

• Working as Data Science Intern on a Finance Project.

#### Aug 2015 - Nov 2016

Bengaluru, India

#### Support Head - Retail and Handheld Billing Solutions,

Wep Solutions Limited ☑

#### Roles and Responsibilities

- Develop support plans to achieve the company's revenue goal and customer satisfaction goals.
- Analyze data to plan the demand and future projections.
- Monitor product failure and quality trends and plan actionable.
- Develop support strategies for customer satisfaction
- Develops support plans and policies for new region development and customer support.
- Travel pan India to meet authorized sales & service partners and end customers regarding post-sales issues, partner meet, and training.
- Handled a team of 12 people across various domains like services, logistics, testing, training, and vendor development.

Apr 2015 – Jul 2015 Bengaluru, India

# **Product Specialist - Retail Billing Solutions**, Wep Solutions Limited ☑ **Roles and Responsibilities**

- Works closely with marketing and R&D teams and finalize the customizations in existing products.
- Conducts the QA, pilot launch, and other tests for new product development.
- Tests the software for any bug and approves the same for final production.
- Travel pan India to meet authorized sales & service partners and end customers regarding product performance reports and also plans their regular training.

Aug 2014 – Mar 2015 Bengaluru, India

# **Service Coordinator** - **Retail Billing Solutions**, Wep Solutions Limited ☑ **Roles and Responsibilities**

- Maintain TAT for service calls
- Plans quarterly spares availability in different service centers
- Provides quarterly corporate training to the Support Team, Sales Managers authorized Dealers and Service providers regarding new product developments and developments in the existing products.



#### **SKILLS**

- Demand Generation

- Data Analytics
- Marketing Operations

• HTML

• CSS

- MS Excel
- Project Management

Python

Pandas

• Numpy

Matplotlib

Seaborn

Tableau

• SQL

Deep Learning

- Machine Learning
- Natural Language Processing

• Email Marketing



### **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Punjabi



**Data Science Architecture** 

from iNeuron

Power BI Masters 🗆

from iNeuron

**Deep Learning Master** 

from iNeuron

**Statistics** ☑ from iNeuron

Tableau Masters 🖸

from iNeuron

### **INTERESTS**

- Learn latest technology trends
- English Grammer
- Play Piano and Guitar

- Indian History
- Indian Constitution